<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="jesscee.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="jesscee.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-12-17T05:44:39+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jessica Chapman Portfolio</title><subtitle>Jess Portfolio of work</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Digital Identity website</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/digitalidentity/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Identity website" /><published>2020-11-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-11-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/digitalidentity</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/digitalidentity/">{% include project-detail.html %}



&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;lead&quot;&gt;An exciting project to be a part of. Building the official public website for the Australian Government's Digital Identity was very rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Website design and development&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Digital Identity website was developed using Drupal 8. The design and theme was customised using the Australian Government Design System as guidance, ensuring that WCAG 2.1 Guidelines (Level AA) were adhered to. Making sure content is accessibile should always be a top priority for any website project. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;mb-5&quot;&gt;The website content, information architecture, and the overall website structure was tested with users to see if users could successfully (and easily) find the information they were seeking. With the user research findings, we were able to make evidence-based content changes. It was extremely valuable to be able to test with users and get insights that we wouldn’t have known had we only tested with internal users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Digital Identity website, showing the design of the homepage&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/digitalidentitywebsite-home.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;





{% include project-nav-footer.html %}

&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Digital Identity website While working at the Digital Transformation Agency, I was the User Experience Design lead, and lead Developer for the Digital Identity website project (putting on my unicorn hat!). Working together with stakeholders, I provided guidance on best-practice, and developed the entire site in Drupal 8. The website was successfully launched in November 2020. Visit digitialidentity.gov.au</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/digitalidentity-thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Engineers Australia</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/engineers-australia/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Engineers Australia" /><published>2018-12-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/ea</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/engineers-australia/">{% include project-detail.html %}
&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row pt-5 pb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12 col-lg-6&quot;&gt;
            &lt;h2&gt;Engineers Australia Online Portal&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Engineers Australia had a major redesign to its public website. The website was given a modern look and feel, and the overarching structure of the site was improved.
            &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
            Engineers Australia's online customer Portal was not included in the redesign. This caused a jarring experience for users when transitioning between the website and Portal.
            &lt;p&gt;
                As the UX designer, I was responsible for improving the user experience of the Portal. We had a lot of feedback from existing users about their experience using the Portal (this was a great starting point!). There were a lot of pain-point areas for users that had to do with poor navigation. This project was not just about redesigning the Portal. There was clear evidence that we needed to fix the information architecture as well.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                I arranged workshops with stakeholders to discuss how we might make the experience better for users. The next stage involved design iteration, prototyping, and testing assumptions with users.
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12 col-lg-6 pt-3&quot;&gt;  

            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Engineers Australia's Portal redesign: showing the Portal homepage&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/ea-portal-application.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid img-border&quot;&gt;
          
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;h2&gt;Online Chartered application&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;I was the design lead for EA's online &quot;Chartered&quot; (a status you can achieve as an engineer) application. The application had to cater for non-members, members, and staff (assessors) to manage applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
There was an existing online application for Chartered, but it was very outdated and clunky (a lot of user dropouts). The application was in need of a redesign and enhancement to the experience. That's where I came in: working with stakeholders, I helped redesign the application. From wireframing, hi-fidelity prototyping right through to front-end development. I was responsible for getting the design created and developed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
There was a lot of work involved in this project, as it wasn't only a redesign of the look and feel. It was an entire redesign of the user journey. This project had a very tight deadline, but the team worked hard and delivered a successful application on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Engineers Australia Chartered Application&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/ea-application01.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Engineers Australia Chartered Application&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/ea-industryreview.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Online Chartered application (staff mangement)&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Engineers Australia Chartered Application&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/ea-application03.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;h2&gt;Online Chartered application (third party management)&lt;/h2&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Engineers Australia Chartered Application&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/ea-application02.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
   
    
    {% include project-nav-footer.html %}
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Next project Engineers Australia While working at Engineers Australia (EA), I was responsible for enhancing the user experience of EA's online offerings. My role also involved designing user interfaces, and the front-end development of these interfaces. I really enjoy hybrid roles where I can use a mixture of my skills to bring a product to life! Visit Engineers Australia website Engineers Australia Online Portal Engineers Australia had a major redesign to its public website. The website was given a modern look and feel, and the overarching structure of the site was improved. Engineers Australia's online customer Portal was not included in the redesign. This caused a jarring experience for users when transitioning between the website and Portal. As the UX designer, I was responsible for improving the user experience of the Portal. We had a lot of feedback from existing users about their experience using the Portal (this was a great starting point!). There were a lot of pain-point areas for users that had to do with poor navigation. This project was not just about redesigning the Portal. There was clear evidence that we needed to fix the information architecture as well. I arranged workshops with stakeholders to discuss how we might make the experience better for users. The next stage involved design iteration, prototyping, and testing assumptions with users.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/ea_thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Defence Housing Australia</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/dha/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Defence Housing Australia" /><published>2018-11-19T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/dha</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/dha/">{% include project-detail.html %}

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row pt-5 pb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
            &lt;h2&gt;DHA Online Services&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;I was responsible for the redesign of DHA's Online Services. This involved modernising the look and feel, making the interface responsive, and improving the user experience for defence members by addressing user pain points. Consistent feedback from members told us the interface was difficult to navigate and users could not find what they needed to access.
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-md&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Defence Housing Australia's Online Services application&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dha-os.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid pb-3&quot;&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;The new UI addressed the product's user needs, such as:
                &lt;ul&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;make it easy for me to know my housing details.&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;make it easy for me to get access to housing services.&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;li&gt;make it easy for me to find new properties, so I have a place to live when I'm deployed.&lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-md-6 pb-4&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;An iPhone mockup that displays DHA's Online Services Application. The application screen shows a user's dashboard which features their current housing accommodation. There are also links to access accommodation options.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dha-mobile-app.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row pt-5 pb-3&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
            &lt;h2&gt;Kiosk App UI&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Sometimes defence members don't have internet access or reliable internet connection when deployed to regional areas. As DHA's Online Services is primarily online, it became increasingly apparent that users needed access to DHA's online services when visting a regional DHA Member Service branch.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;We spoke to users in regional areas, and asked them how we might help make access to online services easier for them. We found that there was a desire for users to be able to do tasks themselves, but still get help if needed. As a potential solution, we trialed using kiosks (locked-down iPad on a stand) in reigonal DHA Member Service branches. This was a relatiely quick fix, and if it worked, would be very cost-effective to roll-out.
         
         &lt;p&gt;The kiosk trial worked very well, with members providing positive feedback. I designed a simple Kiosk user interface to accomodate entry into DHA's Online Services, and informational tutorials related to using DHA Online Services. 

            &lt;p&gt;Members in regional areas that may not have internet, now have access to DHA's Online Services.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row pt-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-md pb-3&quot; style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;video-border&quot;&gt;
                &lt;div class=&quot;video-container au-responsive-media-vid au-responsive-media-vid--16x9&quot;&gt;
                    &lt;video width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; controls class=&quot;au-responsive-media-vid__item&quot;&gt;
                        &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/img/full/Final_HowToScanDocuments.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot;&gt;
                        Your browser does not support the video tag.
                    &lt;/video&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/how-to-scan-video-transcript.html&quot;&gt;Video text transcript&lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-md&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;User interface design of Defence Housing Australia's Kiosk app. The design is presented on an iPad mockup. The design shows the landing page of the app, which features a house in the background with beautiful autumn leaves. There are four options presented to the user: Login now, what can I do, How to use and Location Spotlight.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dha-kiosk.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-border img-fluid&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row pt-5 pb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
            &lt;h2&gt;DHA public website&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;DHA's Online Services's user interface was updated, so there was a need (from a branding perspective) to align the design of the DHA public website to be consistent with DHA'S Online Services.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;I was the project lead and liaised with different areas of DHA to ensure that requirements were being met when redesigning the website. As DHA is a government website, it was important for the website to adhere to WCAG 2.0 Accessibility guidelines. To ensure the DHA website met WCAG 2.0, content changes and semantic code changes were a fundamental part of this project.
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-md&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Defence Housing Australia website, showing the design of the homepage&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dha-home-full.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid img-border&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;col-md&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Defence Housing Australia's Online Services app showing the UI for where users can search for new homes.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dha-homefind.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
            &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Defence Housing Australia website, showing the design of a property listing page&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dha-content-2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    {% include project-nav-footer.html %}
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Next project Defence Housing Australia While working at Defence Housing Australia (DHA), I helped redesign and development DHA's public-facing website, deisgn the UI for DHA's online services application, and assist in designing users interfaces for various other applications and systems. Visit DHA website</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/dha_thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Urban Roasters</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/urbanroasters/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Urban Roasters" /><published>2018-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/urban-roasters</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/urbanroasters/">{% include project-detail.html %}
&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Website design and development&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I built a highly-customised e-commerce website for Urban Roasters. The website helps people easily purchase once-off coffee and coffee subscription orders online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mb-5&quot;&gt;I also designed the theme and suite of user interface patterns for Urban Roasters, ensuring a consistent look and feel across their e-commerce platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;A screenshot of the Urban Roasters website homepage. The design is dark, with subtle graffiti artwork in the background. The graffiti artwork features a wolf hand that is holding a takeaway coffee cup with 'UR' text branding.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/ur-website-home.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Logo design&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;mb-5&quot;&gt;I designed a unique logo for Urban Roasters. The &quot;UR&quot; logo mark subtley hints at coffee beans with the applied shape, while also incorporating the initials of the business name (Urban Roasters).
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Urban Roasters logo design. The logo features 'UR' text stylised on the right. 'Urban Roasters' text is aligned to the left.&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/ur-logo.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

{% include project-nav-footer.html %}
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Next project Urban roasters Urban Roasters is a boutique coffee roastery located in Canberra. This project involved the design and creation of the Urban Roasters logo along with custom graffiti-style artwork. Urban Roasters did not have an existing online presence, and so I was in charge of the full design and development of Urban Roaster's online coffee store. Visit urbanroasters.com.au</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/ur_thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Cove</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/the-cove/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Cove" /><published>2017-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-12-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/cove</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/the-cove/">{% include project-detail.html %}
&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of The Cove website, showing the design of the homepage&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/cove_01.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of The Cove website, showing the design of a content page&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/cove_02.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

{% include project-nav-footer.html %}

&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Next project The Cove The Cove is an online professional development network for the Australian Army. This project involved the full design and development of the Cove website. Visit the Cove website</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/cove_thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Defence Community Hub</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/dch/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Defence Community Hub" /><published>2017-06-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-06-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/dch</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/dch/">{% include project-detail.html %}

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Defence Community Hub website, showing the design of the homepage&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dch-home.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Defence Community Hub website, showing the design of a content page&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/dch-content.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

{% include project-nav-footer.html %}

&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Next project Defence Community Hub An online resource for ADF members and their families to find information on their posting location. This project involved the full design and development of a website using Drupal 7 (GovCMS distribution). Visit Defence Community Hub website</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/dch_thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Guest Designs</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/guest-designs/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Guest Designs" /><published>2017-05-17T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2017-05-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/guestdesigns</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/guest-designs/">{% include project-detail.html %}
&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Guest Designs website, showing the design of the homepage&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/guestdesigns-home.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Guest Designs website, showing the design of a content page&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/guestdesigns-content.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

{% include project-nav-footer.html %}

&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Next project Guest Designs A brochure website created for a local building company in Canberra. This project included the design and development of the Guest Designs website, including logo creation. Visit Guest Designs website</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/guestdesigns_thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">3R Supplements</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/3r/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="3R Supplements" /><published>2016-07-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-07-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/3r</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/3r/">{% include project-detail.html %}

&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Website design and front-end development&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of 3R Supplements website, showing the design of the homepage&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/3r-home.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid img-border&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of 3R Supplements website, showing the design of the main shop page&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/3r-product.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

{% include project-nav-footer.html %}

&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Previous project Next project 3R Supplements 3R Supplements is a Canberra-based company that produces protein supplements. This project involved the design and front-end development of the 3R Supplements online store. Visit 3R Supplements website</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/3r_thumb.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Le Très Bon</title><link href="jesscee.github.io/letresbon/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Le Très Bon" /><published>2015-02-02T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2015-02-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>jesscee.github.io/letresbon</id><content type="html" xml:base="jesscee.github.io/letresbon/">{% include project-detail.html %}
&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cooking Tours&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Le Très Bon website, showing the design of the tour page&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/letresbon-tour.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;col mb-5&quot;&gt;
        &lt;img alt=&quot;Screenshot of Le Très Bon website, showing the design of the tour page&quot; src=&quot;/assets/img/full/letresbon-tour2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot;&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



{% include project-nav-footer.html %}
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Next project Le Très Bon Le Très Bon is a french restaurant located in Bungendore NSW. I designed and developed the restaurant's website, with a particular emphasis on the restaurant's Cooking Tour offerings. Visit Le Très Bon website Cooking Tours</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="jesscee.github.io/letresbon_thumb.jpg" /></entry></feed>